<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Much ado about alot]]></title>
  <link href="http://nisgits.net/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://nisgits.net/"/>
  <updated>2013-04-06T01:00:17+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://nisgits.net/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Stig Kleppe-Jørgensen]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a chat-with-me widget]]></title>
    <link href="http://nisgits.net/blog/2011/12/29/create-a-chat-with-me-widget/"/>
    <updated>2011-12-29T17:13:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://nisgits.net/blog/2011/12/29/create-a-chat-with-me-widget</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever wanted to create a chat-with-me widget on your blog or
just on a regular web page, look no further! Here are the 3 easy steps
for creating a GTalk widget that can easily be included on any web
page.</p>

<p>First, a pre-requisite: you must have a Google account. I guess most
of us already have one&#8230;</p>

<p>Then, the steps:</p>

<ol>
<li>Go to the <a href="http://www.google.com/talk/service/badge/New">Google Talk chatback badge page</a></li>
<li>Copy the generated HTML code into your blog/web site</li>
<li>&#8230;</li>
</ol>


<p>Actually, that was just 2 steps, not 3. My bad.</p>

<p>There is one interesting thing about this chat widget: your visitor
does not need a Google account to use it, but will just appear as a
guest in the chat. Nice and easy for the visitor, but for you it
might be problematic not knowing the visitor&#8217;s identity.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First shot, part deux]]></title>
    <link href="http://nisgits.net/blog/2011/10/25/first-shot-2/"/>
    <updated>2011-10-25T23:28:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://nisgits.net/blog/2011/10/25/first-shot-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So, almost 7 months later I&#8217;ve finally managed to drag myself into a blog posting &#8220;position&#8221;.
Hopefully this wont be the pattern for how long it will be between posts. It&#8217;s not that I don&#8217;t
have anything to say, it&#8217;s more that I have too much to say and can never bear the thought of
writing <em>all</em> of it down. Note to self: just write some of it down, then!</p>

<p>And now taking up the thread from the first post: <a href="http://jekyllrb.com/">Jekyll</a> was the blogging
engine I found which made me want to write a blog again. Then I was derailed, got mixed up with
bad boys like <a href="http://nanoc.stoneship.org">nanoc</a> and <a href="http://nestacms.com">Nesta CMS</a> and ended up
just being confused. What should I choose?</p>

<p><a href="http://octopress.org">Octopress</a> came to my rescue! I had looked at it before, but that was pre-2.0
days. Now it just shines with great design and a lot of great features. One of the greatest are the
very nice options for sharing code snippets&#8230;my code has never looked better! And it is still
Jekyll-based.</p>

<p>Now it is just finding out the theme for the next post. What about saying something about how to
get Chef to work properly under Windows, with package management and all?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First shot]]></title>
    <link href="http://nisgits.net/blog/2011/03/29/first-shot/"/>
    <updated>2011-03-29T23:28:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://nisgits.net/blog/2011/03/29/first-shot</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yes&#8230;finally I&#8217;ve found what I&#8217;ve been looking for! Or maybe not&#8230;that is, I was not actually
looking for it. It just jumped down in front of me.</p>

<p>What I am talking about? Well&#8230;you&#8217;re kinda looking at it. Yes, it is this blog, or more exact,
what I use to create this blog&#8230;</p>

<p>Sorry&#8230;it is late, so I need to continue this another day, I&#8217;m afraid.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
